{
    "quizzes": {
        "-OS-YXhSm6VaFpKATTWx": {
            "createdAt": 1749134748678,
            "level": 1,
            "points": 20,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "answerType": "manual",
                    "correctAnswer": "22",
                    "explanation": "7 plus 15 equals 22.",
                    "point": 1,
                    "questionText": "7 + 15",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "answerType": "manual",
                    "correctAnswer": "45",
                    "explanation": "27 plus 18 equals 45.",
                    "point": 1,
                    "questionText": "27 + 18",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "updatedAt": 1749134748678
        }
    },
    "rooms": {
        "-OSEkJbvwsbjt0hpSvsL": {
            "code": "C86HU",
            "createdAt": 1749389757057,
            "currentPlayerCount": 1,
            "currentQuestion": 0,
            "gameStartedAt": 1749389778309,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749389778311,
            "maxPlayers": 4,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749389771661,
                    "lastActivity": 1749389775086,
                    "name": "miteshhq",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0
                }
            },
            "questionStartedAt": 1749389776844,
            "questionTimeLimit": 15,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "26",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "33 − 7",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "22",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "7 + 15",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "145",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "100 + 45",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "42",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "6 × 7",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "36",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "9 × 4",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "528",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "88 × 6",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "45",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "50 − 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "261",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "29 × 9",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "325",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "65 × 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "100",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "125 − 25",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "roomName": "Ragnar",
            "status": "playing",
            "totalQuestions": 10
        },
        "-OSEkaTcmPR_xGwXh-QP": {
            "code": "ZQQHA",
            "createdAt": 1749389830216,
            "currentPlayerCount": 2,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749389833048,
            "matchmakingRoom": true,
            "maxPlayers": 2,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749389830216,
                    "name": "Host",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0
                },
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": false,
                    "joinedAt": 1749389833048,
                    "name": "ragnar",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0
                }
            },
            "roomName": "Quick Battle 1749389829370",
            "status": "waiting"
        },
        "-OSEn5c9OqENhjPmyLLv": {
            "code": "UTU55",
            "createdAt": 1749390486321,
            "currentPlayerCount": 2,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749390490178,
            "matchmakingRoom": true,
            "maxPlayers": 2,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749390486321,
                    "name": "Host",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0
                },
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": false,
                    "joinedAt": 1749390490178,
                    "name": "ragnar",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0
                }
            },
            "roomName": "Quick Battle 1749390485287",
            "status": "waiting"
        },
        "-OSEnUHEx4tpf_lvIjpd": {
            "code": "K8PPL",
            "createdAt": 1749390587172,
            "currentPlayerCount": 1,
            "currentQuestion": 0,
            "gameStartedAt": 1749390598807,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749390599527,
            "maxPlayers": 4,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749390594225,
                    "lastActivity": 1749390596010,
                    "name": "miteshhq",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                }
            },
            "questionStartedAt": 1749390597511,
            "questionTimeLimit": 15,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "35",
                    "explanation": "12 plus 23 equals 35.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "12 + 23",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "100",
                    "explanation": "135 minus 35 equals 100.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "135 − 35",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "24",
                    "explanation": "36 minus 12 equals 24.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "36 − 12",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "26",
                    "explanation": "14 plus 12 equals 26.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "14 + 12",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "100",
                    "explanation": "75 plus 25 equals 100.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "75 + 25",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "459",
                    "explanation": "51 multiplied by 9 equals 459.",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "51 × 9",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "100",
                    "explanation": "144 minus 44 equals 100.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "144 − 44",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "500",
                    "explanation": "550 minus 50 equals 500.",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "550 − 50",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "140",
                    "explanation": "70 plus 70 equals 140.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "70 + 70",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "40",
                    "explanation": "8 multiplied by 5 equals 40.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "8 × 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "roomName": "Ragnar",
            "status": "playing",
            "totalQuestions": 10
        },
        "-OSEqI0jUkof47ngdfZF": {
            "code": "FV1Q4",
            "createdAt": 1749391323391,
            "currentPlayerCount": 2,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1",
            "lastActivity": 1749391326748,
            "matchmakingRoom": true,
            "maxPlayers": 2,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": false,
                    "joinedAt": 1749391326748,
                    "name": "miteshhq",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0
                },
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749391323391,
                    "name": "Host",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0
                }
            },
            "roomName": "Quick Battle 1749391321997",
            "status": "waiting"
        },
        "-OSErMVpssAVkAwJu_Zz": {
            "code": "LCIRH",
            "createdAt": 1749391603915,
            "currentPlayerCount": 1,
            "currentQuestion": 0,
            "gameStartedAt": 1749391617630,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1",
            "lastActivity": 1749391618377,
            "maxPlayers": 4,
            "players": {
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749391612576,
                    "lastActivity": 1749391615735,
                    "name": "ragnar",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                }
            },
            "questionStartedAt": 1749391616958,
            "questionTimeLimit": 15,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "480",
                    "explanation": "60 multiplied by 8 equals 480.",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "60 × 8",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "462",
                    "explanation": "66 multiplied by 7 equals 462.",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "66 × 7",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "385",
                    "explanation": "35 multiplied by 11 equals 385.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "35 × 11",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "170",
                    "explanation": "90 plus 80 equals 170.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "90 + 80",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "144",
                    "explanation": "48 multiplied by 3 equals 144.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "48 × 3",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "145",
                    "explanation": "150 minus 5 equals 145.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "150 − 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "450",
                    "explanation": "90 multiplied by 5 equals 450.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "90 × 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "210",
                    "explanation": "150 plus 60 equals 210.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "150 + 60",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "270",
                    "explanation": "45 multiplied by 6 equals 270.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "45 × 6",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "450",
                    "explanation": "30 multiplied by 15 equals 450.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "30 × 15",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "roomName": "Djjdjd",
            "status": "playing",
            "totalQuestions": 10
        },
        "-OSEu4FypkhFnstrRGvG": {
            "code": "8P5T0",
            "createdAt": 1749392315612,
            "currentPlayerCount": 2,
            "currentQuestion": 0,
            "gameStartedAt": 1749392320890,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749392320890,
            "matchmakingRoom": true,
            "maxPlayers": 2,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "answer": "4",
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749392315612,
                    "name": "Host",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                },
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": false,
                    "joinedAt": 1749392319635,
                    "name": "ragnar",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                }
            },
            "questionStartedAt": 1749392320238,
            "questionTimeLimit": 15,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "480",
                    "explanation": "60 multiplied by 8 equals 480.",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "60 × 8",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "272",
                    "explanation": "34 multiplied by 8 equals 272.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "34 × 8",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "210",
                    "explanation": "15 multiplied by 14 equals 210.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "15 × 14",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "300",
                    "explanation": "50 multiplied by 6 equals 300.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "50 × 6",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "450",
                    "explanation": "30 multiplied by 15 equals 450.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "30 × 15",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "441",
                    "explanation": "49 multiplied by 9 equals 441.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "49 × 9",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "230",
                    "explanation": "200 plus 30 equals 230.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "200 + 30",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "200",
                    "explanation": "230 minus 30 equals 200.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "230 − 30",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "120",
                    "explanation": "60 plus 60 equals 120.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "60 + 60",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "196",
                    "explanation": "49 multiplied by 4 equals 196.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "49 × 4",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "roomName": "Quick Battle 1749392314757",
            "status": "playing",
            "totalQuestions": 10
        },
        "-OSEuJrBgD4r7_obR1pd": {
            "code": "E2YC8",
            "createdAt": 1749392379476,
            "currentPlayerCount": 0,
            "currentQuestion": 0,
            "gameStartedAt": 1749392411896,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1",
            "lastActivity": 1749392436447,
            "maxPlayers": 4,
            "players": {
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "answer": "2",
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749392408750,
                    "name": "ragnar",
                    "ready": false,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                }
            },
            "questionStartedAt": 1749392411232,
            "questionTimeLimit": 15,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "22",
                    "explanation": "7 plus 15 equals 22.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "7 + 15",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "8",
                    "explanation": "32 divided by 4 equals 8.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "32 ÷ 4",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "150",
                    "explanation": "75 multiplied by 2 equals 150.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "75 × 2",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "363",
                    "explanation": "33 multiplied by 11 equals 363.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "33 × 11",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "145",
                    "explanation": "150 minus 5 equals 145.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "150 − 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "100",
                    "explanation": "120 minus 20 equals 100.",
                    "points": 2,
                    "question": "120 − 20",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "196",
                    "explanation": "49 multiplied by 4 equals 196.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "49 × 4",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "400",
                    "explanation": "80 multiplied by 5 equals 400.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "80 × 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "392",
                    "explanation": "49 multiplied by 8 equals 392.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "49 × 8",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "230",
                    "explanation": "200 plus 30 equals 230.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "200 + 30",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "roomName": "Cvv",
            "status": "playing",
            "totalQuestions": 10
        },
        "-OSEuZRZakMUUrgCmmge": {
            "code": "40GHU",
            "createdAt": 1749392443294,
            "currentPlayerCount": 1,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749392443294,
            "maxPlayers": 4,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749392443294,
                    "name": "Host",
                    "ready": false,
                    "score": 0
                }
            },
            "roomName": "Bbxndbc",
            "status": "waiting"
        },
        "-OSEwsQq9726lwC2hxLd": {
            "code": "RPUQI",
            "createdAt": 1749393049482,
            "currentPlayerCount": 2,
            "currentQuestion": 0,
            "gameStartedAt": 1749393053669,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749393053669,
            "matchmakingRoom": true,
            "maxPlayers": 2,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "answer": "",
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749393049482,
                    "name": "Host",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                },
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": false,
                    "joinedAt": 1749393052442,
                    "name": "ragnar",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                }
            },
            "questionStartedAt": 1749393053014,
            "questionTimeLimit": 15,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "432",
                    "explanation": "54 multiplied by 8 equals 432.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "54 × 8",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "8",
                    "explanation": "32 divided by 4 equals 8.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "32 ÷ 4",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "270",
                    "explanation": "45 multiplied by 6 equals 270.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "45 × 6",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "210",
                    "explanation": "14 multiplied by 15 equals 210.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "14 × 15",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "22",
                    "explanation": "7 plus 15 equals 22.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "7 + 15",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "300",
                    "explanation": "50 multiplied by 6 equals 300.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "50 × 6",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "400",
                    "explanation": "80 multiplied by 5 equals 400.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "80 × 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "196",
                    "explanation": "49 multiplied by 4 equals 196.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "49 × 4",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "175",
                    "explanation": "35 multiplied by 5 equals 175.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "35 × 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "42",
                    "explanation": "6 multiplied by 7 equals 42.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "6 × 7",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "roomName": "Quick Battle 1749393048658",
            "status": "playing",
            "totalQuestions": 10
        },
        "-OSExSc9zJG0-VgKieZs": {
            "code": "RZWJV",
            "createdAt": 1749393201802,
            "currentPlayerCount": 2,
            "currentQuestion": 0,
            "gameStartedAt": 1749393251168,
            "gameState": {
                "currentRound": 0,
                "timeLeft": 0,
                "totalRounds": 5
            },
            "hostId": "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2",
            "lastActivity": 1749393251168,
            "maxPlayers": 4,
            "players": {
                "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": true,
                    "joinedAt": 1749393201802,
                    "name": "Host",
                    "ready": false,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                },
                "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
                    "connected": true,
                    "isHost": false,
                    "joinedAt": 1749393243325,
                    "lastActivity": 1749393248346,
                    "name": "ragnar",
                    "ready": true,
                    "score": 0,
                    "winner": false
                }
            },
            "questionStartedAt": 1749393250509,
            "questionTimeLimit": 15,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "260",
                    "explanation": "300 minus 40 equals 260.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "300 − 40",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "472",
                    "explanation": "59 multiplied by 8 equals 472.",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "59 × 8",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "175",
                    "explanation": "200 minus 25 equals 175.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "200 − 25",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "450",
                    "explanation": "75 multiplied by 6 equals 450.",
                    "points": 6,
                    "question": "75 × 6",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "252",
                    "explanation": "36 multiplied by 7 equals 252.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "36 × 7",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "220",
                    "explanation": "250 minus 30 equals 220.",
                    "points": 3,
                    "question": "250 − 30",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "36",
                    "explanation": "9 multiplied by 4 equals 36.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "9 × 4",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "26",
                    "explanation": "14 plus 12 equals 26.",
                    "points": 1,
                    "question": "14 + 12",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "450",
                    "explanation": "90 multiplied by 5 equals 450.",
                    "points": 5,
                    "question": "90 × 5",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                },
                {
                    "correctAnswer": "261",
                    "explanation": "29 multiplied by 9 equals 261.",
                    "points": 4,
                    "question": "29 × 9",
                    "timeLimit": 30
                }
            ],
            "roomName": "Dbbdbdh",
            "status": "playing",
            "totalQuestions": 10
        }
    },
    "users": {
        "1vmBYMCUdEOtaULTxlAUBMI4MMg2": {
            "age": "19",
            "avatar": 2,
            "completedLevels": [
                null,
                true,
                true,
                true,
                true,
                true
            ],
            "currentLevel": 6,
            "email": "miteshhq@gmail.com",
            "fullName": "Miteshh",
            "gender": "Male",
            "highestCompletedLevelCompleted": 1,
            "isnewuser": false,
            "lastCompletionDate": "2025-06-06",
            "phoneNumber": "7897897890",
            "referrals": 7,
            "streak": 0,
            "totalPoints": 1228.5,
            "username": "miteshhq"
        },
        "CcPwQdmCardxx4SPVyMqD2gpM5u1": {
            "avatar": 1,
            "completedLevels": [
                null,
                true
            ],
            "currentLevel": 2,
            "email": "ragnar@mail.com",
            "fullName": "Ragnar Lo",
            "highestCompletedLevelCompleted": 0,
            "isnewuser": false,
            "lastCompletionDate": "2025-06-06",
            "phoneNumber": "7889203083",
            "referrals": 2,
            "streak": 0,
            "totalPoints": 87,
            "username": "ragnar"
        }
    }
}